mobileaction.co 2017-03-14

# Mobile Action - Privacy Policy

###### Last updated: 01/03/2016

We at Mobile Action, Inc. (“Mobile Action,” “we,” “us,” or “our”) created this Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy”) because we know that you care about how information you provide to us is used and shared. This Privacy Policy relates to the information collection and use practices of Mobile Action in connection with our Services which are made available to you through our Site. 

The terms of this Privacy Policy are incorporated by reference in the Terms of Service that you accept upon registration for the Services (the “Terms of Service”). By accepting the Terms of Service, you accept the terms of this Privacy Policy. Capitalized terms not defined in this Privacy Policy shall have the meaning set forth in our Terms of Service. 

We provide app analytics, ASO intelligence, market and usage intelligence so that you can have better insights on your performance and take the right action. Recommended actions tool offers customized suggestions just for you! 

#####  Information We Collect 

We do not collect any personal information from you unless you voluntarily provide it to us.

When you sign up to use the Services, you will be asked to provide us with certain personal information, such as your first name, last name, company name, email address, credit card and other payment related information. In this Privacy Policy, we refer to this information as “Personal Information.”

Like most websites, we use automatic data collection technology when you visit the Site to record information that identifies your computer, to track your use of the Site, and to collect certain basic information about you and your surfing habits. This information includes information about your operating system, your IP addresses, browser type and language, referring and exit pages and URLs, keywords, date and time, amount of time spent on particular pages, what sections of a website you visit, and similar information concerning your use of the Site and the Services (the “Usage Information”). We collect this Usage Information by using cookies and pixel tags (also called web beacons or clear gifs). Cookies are small packets of data that a web site stores on your computer’s hard drive so that your computer will “remember” information about your visit. Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of web site users. You can reject cookies by following the directions provided in your Internet provider’s “help” file. If you reject cookies, you may still visit the Site, but may not be able to use some areas of the Site.

We do not collect Personal Information in this way, but if you’ve provided us with Personal Information we may associate that information with the information that is collected automatically. Automatic data collection may be performed on our behalf by our services providers.

##### How We Use Your Information

We will use your Personal Information and Usage Information for the following purposes:

• To respond to your requests and to provide you with the Services;

• To respond to your inquiries and contact you about changes to the Site, and/or the Services;

• To send you notices (for example, in the form of e-mails, mailings, and the like) regarding products or services you are receiving, and for billing and collection purposes;

• To improve the Site and/or the Services;

• For any other purposes disclosed at the time the information is collected or to which you consent; and

• As otherwise specifically described in this Privacy Policy.

We may also use your information to improve our Site, and/or the Services, and may use cookies and other information to enable us to customize your user experience.

We will share your credit card and other payment related information with a Third Party Service Provider as necessary to process your payment. The Third Party Service Provider stores your credit card information; we do not store this information. Storage by the Third Party Service Provider of your credit card and other payment relating information is subject to the privacy policies and practices of the Third Party Service Provider and is not subject to the terms of this privacy policy. By providing your credit card and other payment related information, you acknowledge and agree to use of such information by the Third Party Service Provider for purposes of processing your payment to us.

We, like many businesses, sometimes hire other companies to perform certain business-related functions. Examples include mailing information, maintaining databases, hosting services, and processing payments. When we employ another company to perform a function of this nature, we provide them with the information that they need to perform their specific function, which may include Personal Information.

If we or all or substantially all of our assets are acquired, we expect that the information that we have collected, including Personal Information, would be transferred along with our other business assets.

We may disclose user information to government authorities, and to other third parties when compelled to do so by government authorities, at our discretion, or otherwise as required by law, including but not limited to in response to court orders and subpoenas. We also may disclose user information when we have reason to believe that someone is or may be causing injury to or interference with our rights or property, other users of the Services, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities.

Other than as set forth herein, we will not share, rent or sell your information to a third party.

##### How We Protect Your Information

We take commercially reasonable steps to protect your Personal Information from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. Please understand, however, that no security system is impenetrable. We cannot guarantee the security of our databases, nor can we guarantee that the information you supply will not be intercepted while being transmitted to and from us over the Internet. In particular, e-mail sent to or from us may not be secure, and you should therefore take special care in deciding what information you send to us via e-mail.

##### Accessing and Modifying Account Information

You may update the information that is stored in your user account by visiting https://dashboard.mobileaction.co/settings/index or by e-mailing us at help@mobileaction.co.

##### Your Choices

If you wish to stop receiving emails from us, please send us a message via help@mobileaction.co. You may also choose to unsubscribe from our emails by following the instructions in the bottom of the email.

##### Links

The Site and the Services may contain content, services, advertising and other materials that link to External Sites. Mobile Action does not endorse and is not responsible for the content of any such External Sites. Please refer to the terms of use and privacy policies of the External Sites for more information.

##### Important Notice to Non-U.S. Residents

The Site and the Services are operated in the United States. If you are located outside of the United States, please be aware that any information you provide to us will be transferred to the United States. By providing us with any information, you consent to this transfer.

##### Children

We do not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under the age of 13 through the Site and/or the Services. If you are under 13, please do not give us any Personal Information. We encourage parents and legal guardians to monitor their children’s Internet usage and to help enforce our Privacy Policy by instructing their children to never provide Personal Information through any website without their permission. If you have reason to believe that a child under the age of 13 has provided Personal Information to us, please contact us, and we will endeavor to delete that information from our databases.

##### Changes to This Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy is effective as of the date stated at the top of this Privacy Policy. We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time with or without notice to you. In any event, you will be required to affirmatively accept the revised Privacy Policy prior to next logging-in to your account.

##### Contact

If you have questions about this Privacy Policy, please send us a message via help@mobileaction.co.
